<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on MLL Electronics</title><link>https://mllelectronics.com/post/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on MLL Electronics</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mllelectronics.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Resume/Shop Space Documentation</title><link>https://mllelectronics.com/p/resume/shop-space-documentation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mllelectronics.com/p/resume/shop-space-documentation/</guid><description>Resume If you are interested in my resume - please download from this link.
Download: pdf
Professional Experience Autonomous Systems Engineer Honda R&amp;amp;D America Marysville , OH Jan 2022 - Present
Led ECU system level development and validation across multiple vehicle models from project kick off to mass production while working cross functionally to define, design and perform tests. Designed and implemented both HILS and on vehicle solutions for validating new and existing regulatory requirements for ECU development.</description></item><item><title>Hardware is Hard</title><link>https://mllelectronics.com/p/hardware-is-hard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mllelectronics.com/p/hardware-is-hard/</guid><description>Introduction to Hardware Hardware. What exactly is it? Why is it important. Why is it hard? Since the dawn of time there has been hardware engineers.
The Midwest is an area known for manufacturing excellence. Its unique geographic location, mild climate, and proximity make it desirable for the development of hardware products. My goal is to explore building hardware in Columbus and its surround areas. I hope you will join me on learning more on my journey to building hardware quicker.</description></item><item><title>Michael Liang - Resume 2021</title><link>https://mllelectronics.com/p/michael-liang-resume-2021/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mllelectronics.com/p/michael-liang-resume-2021/</guid><description>Download: pdf
Seeking a full time position after December 2021.
Michael Liang Skills Rapid Prototyping PCB Design (KiCAD, Eagle) 2D CAD (AutoCAD, NanoCAD) 3D CAD (SolidWorks, Fusion 360) Soldering (SMT rework, through-hole) 3D Printing and Additive manufacturing LabView MATLAB Microcontrollers (STM32, AVR/Atmel, PIC) Programming (C, Python) Professional Experience ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING CO-OP, Toast Inc, Boston MA, Jun 2021 - August 2021
Designed and implemented an automated robotic hardware testing platform for Toast Hardware products.</description></item><item><title>Keyboard Warrior</title><link>https://mllelectronics.com/p/keyboard-warrior/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mllelectronics.com/p/keyboard-warrior/</guid><description>Introduction to Keyboard Warrior This a page about the Keyboard Warrior which was my Senior Project for my Electrical and Electronic engineering degree at the University of Akron.
Hardware Layout &amp;amp; Design Considerations The badge is based on STM32F303RET6 processor which has 26 I/O, builtin 512kB of flash memory, 80kB of RAM, and operates at 3.3 volts with a max clock frequnecy of 72 MHz. Communication and debug on this board consisted of DFU (Device Firmware Update) via USB C and a SWD(Serial Wire debug) port.</description></item><item><title>GCC Laser Reference</title><link>https://mllelectronics.com/p/gcc-laser-reference/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mllelectronics.com/p/gcc-laser-reference/</guid><description>Introduction to the GCC Mercury This a page about the GCC Mercury II laser which is a 30 Watt CO2 laser that has build area of 12&amp;quot;x24&amp;quot;. Parts are still available for this laser however they are becoming rare as time goes on. The purpose of this page is provide reference materials for future owners and operators of this machine.
Hardware Overview The controller is a custom controller made by GCC Mercury and is nearing the end of its useful life.</description></item><item><title>Hackathons</title><link>https://mllelectronics.com/p/hackathons/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mllelectronics.com/p/hackathons/</guid><description>Introduction to Hackathons This a page is a curated selection of hackathon projects that I&amp;rsquo;ve worked on over my 3+ years at the University of Akron. Most of the hacks on this page are hardware based. A large majority of my hacks involve rapid prototyping techniques such as 3d printing, laser cutting and development with the Arduino and ESP32 platforms. As hardware hackers it is not uncommon to carry around a large box of hardware so as a group we decided to build Auto Tank a robotic pack mule for hackathons as featured below.</description></item><item><title>Blimp Badge</title><link>https://mllelectronics.com/p/blimp-badge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mllelectronics.com/p/blimp-badge/</guid><description>Introduction to the Blimp Badge This a page about the Blimp Badge which is a Atmega328p based badge made for the Sophmore career fair at UAkron to showcase my skills in embedded systems design, circuit layout and programming. The badge features a .96&amp;quot; I2C OLED that outputs a QR code my website mllelectronics.com which has my resume and project portfolio on it.
Hardware Layout &amp;amp; Design Considerations The badge is based on Atmega328P and utilzes the internal 8mHz clocking running on 3.</description></item></channel></rss>