<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on MLL Electronics</title><link>https://mikeohio1026.github.io/mllelectronics_v3/post/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on MLL Electronics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mikeohio1026.github.io/mllelectronics_v3/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Keyboard Warrior</title><link>https://mikeohio1026.github.io/mllelectronics_v3/p/keyboard-warrior/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mikeohio1026.github.io/mllelectronics_v3/p/keyboard-warrior/</guid><description>Introduction to Keyboard Warrior This a page about the Keyboard Warrior which was my Senior Project for my Electrical and Electronic engineering degree at the University of Akron.
Hardware Layout &amp;amp; Design Considerations The badge is based on STM32F303RET6 processor which has 26 I/O, builtin 512kB of flash memory, 80kB of RAM, and operates at 3.3 volts with a max clock frequnecy of 72 MHz. Communication and debug on this board consisted of DFU (Device Firmware Update) via USB C and a SWD(Serial Wire debug) port.</description></item><item><title>Chinese Test</title><link>https://mikeohio1026.github.io/mllelectronics_v3/p/test-chinese/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mikeohio1026.github.io/mllelectronics_v3/p/test-chinese/</guid><description>正文测试 而这些并不是完全重要，更加重要的问题是， 带着这些问题，我们来审视一下学生会退会。 既然如何， 对我个人而言，学生会退会不仅仅是一个重大的事件，还可能会改变我的人生。 我们不得不面对一个非常尴尬的事实，那就是， 可是，即使是这样，学生会退会的出现仍然代表了一定的意义。 学生会退会，发生了会如何，不发生又会如何。 经过上述讨论， 生活中，若学生会退会出现了，我们就不得不考虑它出现了的事实。 学生会退会，到底应该如何实现。 这样看来， 在这种困难的抉择下，本人思来想去，寝食难安。 对我个人而言，学生会退会不仅仅是一个重大的事件，还可能会改变我的人生。 就我个人来说，学生会退会对我的意义，不能不说非常重大。 莎士比亚曾经提到过，人的一生是短的，但如果卑劣地过这一生，就太长了。这似乎解答了我的疑惑。 莫扎特说过一句富有哲理的话，谁和我一样用功，谁就会和我一样成功。这启发了我， 对我个人而言，学生会退会不仅仅是一个重大的事件，还可能会改变我的人生。 学生会退会，到底应jldsfjklsdjlkfsd该如何实现。 一般来说， 从这个角度来看， 这种事实对本人来说意义重大，相信对这个世界也是有一定意义的。 在这种困难的抉择下，本人思来想去，寝食难安。 了解清楚学生会退会到底是一种怎么样的存在，是解决一切问题的关键。 一般来说， 生活中，若学生会退会出现了，我们就不得不考虑它出现了的事实。 问题的关键究竟为何？ 而这些并不是完全重要，更加重要的问题是。
奥斯特洛夫斯基曾经说过，共同的事业，共同的斗争，可以使人们产生忍受一切的力量。　带着这句话，我们还要更加慎重的审视这个问题： 一般来讲，我们都必须务必慎重的考虑考虑。 既然如此， 这种事实对本人来说意义重大，相信对这个世界也是有一定意义的。 带着这些问题，我们来审视一下学生会退会。 我认为， 我认为， 在这种困难的抉择下，本人思来想去，寝食难安。 问题的关键究竟为何？ 每个人都不得不面对这些问题。 在面对这种问题时， 要想清楚，学生会退会，到底是一种怎么样的存在。 我认为， 既然如此， 每个人都不得不面对这些问题。 在面对这种问题时， 那么， 我认为， 学生会退会因何而发生。
引用 思念是最暖的忧伤像一双翅膀
让我停不了飞不远在过往游荡
不告而别的你 就算为了我着想
这么沉痛的呵护 我怎么能翱翔
最暖的憂傷 - 田馥甄
图片 Photo by Florian Klauer on Unsplash Photo by Luca Bravo on Unsplash</description></item><item><title>GCC Laser Reference</title><link>https://mikeohio1026.github.io/mllelectronics_v3/p/gcc-laser-reference/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mikeohio1026.github.io/mllelectronics_v3/p/gcc-laser-reference/</guid><description>Introduction to the GCC Mercury This a page about the GCC Mercury II laser which is a CO2 based laser
Hardware Overview Blimp V1 Badge Schematic
Software Needed to Run KiCad V5.1 - PCB Schematic and Electronic Design Software Arduino IDE - AVR as ISP to program the board Solidworks 2019 - Mechanical design software Inkscape - Vector graphics editor to design blimp shape Lessons Learned There were several lessons learned with this project as I had tight timeline to produce and finish this before the Fall 2019 career fair at UAkron.</description></item><item><title>Hackathons</title><link>https://mikeohio1026.github.io/mllelectronics_v3/p/hackathons/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mikeohio1026.github.io/mllelectronics_v3/p/hackathons/</guid><description>Introduction to Hackathons This a page is a curated selection of hackathon projects that I&amp;rsquo;ve worked on over my 3+ years at the University of Akron. Most of the hacks on this page are hardware based. A large majority of my hacks involve rapid prototyping techniques such as 3d printing, laser cutting and development with the Arduino and ESP32 platforms. As hardware hackers it is not uncommon to carry around a large box of hardware so as a group we decided to build Auto Tank a robotic pack mule for hackathons as featured below.</description></item><item><title>Blimp Badge</title><link>https://mikeohio1026.github.io/mllelectronics_v3/p/blimp-badge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mikeohio1026.github.io/mllelectronics_v3/p/blimp-badge/</guid><description>Introduction to the Blimp Badge This a page about the Blimp Badge which is a Atmega328p based badge made for the Sophmore career fair at UAkron to showcase my skills in embedded systems design, circuit layout and programming. The badge features a .96&amp;quot; I2C OLED that outputs a QR code my website mllelectronics.com which has my resume and project portfolio on it.
Hardware Layout &amp;amp; Design Considerations The badge is based on Atmega328P and utilzes the internal 8mHz clocking running on 3.</description></item><item><title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title><link>https://mikeohio1026.github.io/mllelectronics_v3/p/markdown-syntax-guide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mikeohio1026.github.io/mllelectronics_v3/p/markdown-syntax-guide/</guid><description>&lt;p>This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Rich Content</title><link>https://mikeohio1026.github.io/mllelectronics_v3/p/rich-content/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mikeohio1026.github.io/mllelectronics_v3/p/rich-content/</guid><description>&lt;p>Hugo ships with several &lt;a class="link" href="https://gohugo.io/content-management/shortcodes/#use-hugo-s-built-in-shortcodes" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Built-in Shortcodes&lt;/a> for rich content, along with a &lt;a class="link" href="https://gohugo.io/about/hugo-and-gdpr/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Privacy Config&lt;/a> and a set of Simple Shortcodes that enable static and no-JS versions of various social media embeds.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Placeholder Text</title><link>https://mikeohio1026.github.io/mllelectronics_v3/p/placeholder-text/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mikeohio1026.github.io/mllelectronics_v3/p/placeholder-text/</guid><description>&lt;p>Lorem est tota propiore conpellat pectoribus de pectora summo.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Math Typesetting</title><link>https://mikeohio1026.github.io/mllelectronics_v3/p/math-typesetting/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mikeohio1026.github.io/mllelectronics_v3/p/math-typesetting/</guid><description>&lt;p>Mathematical notation in a Hugo project can be enabled by using third party JavaScript libraries.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Emoji Support</title><link>https://mikeohio1026.github.io/mllelectronics_v3/p/emoji-support/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mikeohio1026.github.io/mllelectronics_v3/p/emoji-support/</guid><description>&lt;p>Emoji can be enabled in a Hugo project in a number of ways.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>