<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Electronics on MLL Electronics</title><link>https://mllelectronics.com/tags/electronics/</link><description>Recent content in Electronics on MLL Electronics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mllelectronics.com/tags/electronics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hardware is Hard</title><link>https://mllelectronics.com/p/hardware-is-hard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mllelectronics.com/p/hardware-is-hard/</guid><description>Introduction to Hardware Hardware. What exactly is it? Why is it important. Why is it hard? Since the dawn of time there has been hardware engineers.
The Midwest is an area known for manufacturing excellence. Its unique geographic location, mild climate, and proximity make it desirable for the development of hardware products.
The V Model of Hardware and Software Development:
This model of software development was established by both Germany and the United States in the late 1980s as a way to effectively manage projects.</description></item><item><title>Posts</title><link>https://mllelectronics.com/post/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mllelectronics.com/post/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Keyboard Warrior</title><link>https://mllelectronics.com/p/keyboard-warrior/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mllelectronics.com/p/keyboard-warrior/</guid><description>Introduction to Keyboard Warrior This a page about the Keyboard Warrior which was my Senior Project for my Electrical and Electronic engineering degree at the University of Akron.
Hardware Layout &amp;amp; Design Considerations The badge is based on STM32F303RET6 processor which has 26 I/O, builtin 512kB of flash memory, 80kB of RAM, and operates at 3.3 volts with a max clock frequnecy of 72 MHz. Communication and debug on this board consisted of DFU (Device Firmware Update) via USB C and a SWD(Serial Wire debug) port.</description></item><item><title>Hackathons</title><link>https://mllelectronics.com/p/hackathons/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mllelectronics.com/p/hackathons/</guid><description>Introduction to Hackathons This a page is a curated selection of hackathon projects that I&amp;rsquo;ve worked on over my 3+ years at the University of Akron. Most of the hacks on this page are hardware based. A large majority of my hacks involve rapid prototyping techniques such as 3d printing, laser cutting and development with the Arduino and ESP32 platforms. As hardware hackers it is not uncommon to carry around a large box of hardware so as a group we decided to build Auto Tank a robotic pack mule for hackathons as featured below.</description></item><item><title>Blimp Badge</title><link>https://mllelectronics.com/p/blimp-badge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mllelectronics.com/p/blimp-badge/</guid><description>Introduction to the Blimp Badge This a page about the Blimp Badge which is a Atmega328p based badge made for the Sophmore career fair at UAkron to showcase my skills in embedded systems design, circuit layout and programming. The badge features a .96&amp;quot; I2C OLED that outputs a QR code my website mllelectronics.com which has my resume and project portfolio on it.
Hardware Layout &amp;amp; Design Considerations The badge is based on Atmega328P and utilzes the internal 8mHz clocking running on 3.</description></item></channel></rss>