<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hardware Development on MLL Electronics</title><link>https://mllelectronics.com/categories/hardware-development/</link><description>Recent content in Hardware Development on MLL Electronics</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mllelectronics.com/categories/hardware-development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Resume/Shop Space Documentation</title><link>https://mllelectronics.com/p/resume/shop-space-documentation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mllelectronics.com/p/resume/shop-space-documentation/</guid><description>Resume If you are interested in my resume - please downland from this link. Download: pdf
Focused on building products and prototypes quickly in my free time. Developing a strong capability both electrically and mechanically. Split into an Electronics lab with additive manufacturing capability and 2000 sq ft shop space with equipment/tools and machines need for general fabrication and automotive repair.
Some Highlights include:
Electronics Fab
Programmable Power supplies - GPIB/Serial/Analog Data Aquisition units - Fluke Hydra II DAQ, HP Programmable AC/DC Multimeter Oscilloscopes: Tektronix 100 mHz dual chanel analog, Siglent 50 mhZ dual channel digital Hakko FX888D Soldering Station Generic Chinese Hot Air reflow station Circuit Specialist - Reflow board preheated Wiring harness fab tools Automotive harness Automation panels MLL Electronics Reflow oven *Still in development - custom reflow controller Metal Working/General Fab</description></item><item><title>Hardware is Hard</title><link>https://mllelectronics.com/p/hardware-is-hard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mllelectronics.com/p/hardware-is-hard/</guid><description>Introduction to Hardware Hardware. What exactly is it? Why is it important. Why is it hard? Since the dawn of time there has been hardware engineers.
The Midwest is an area known for manufacturing excellence. Its unique geographic location, mild climate, and proximity make it desirable for the development of hardware products. My goal is to explore building hardware in Columbus and its surround areas. I hope you will join me on learning more on my journey to building hardware quicker.</description></item></channel></rss>