<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hardware Development on MLL Electronics</title><link>https://mllelectronics.com/categories/hardware-development/</link><description>Recent content in Hardware Development on MLL Electronics</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mllelectronics.com/categories/hardware-development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Resume/Shop Space Documentation</title><link>https://mllelectronics.com/p/resume/shop-space-documentation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mllelectronics.com/p/resume/shop-space-documentation/</guid><description>Resume If you are interested in my resume - please download from this link.
Download: pdf
Professional Experience Autonomous Systems Engineer Honda R&amp;amp;D America : Marysville , OH Jan 2022 - Present
Led ECU system level development and validation across multiple vehicle models from project kick off to mass production while working cross functionally to define, design and perform tests. Designed and implemented both HILS and on vehicle solutions for validating new and existing regulatory requirements for ECU development.</description></item><item><title>Hardware is Hard</title><link>https://mllelectronics.com/p/hardware-is-hard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mllelectronics.com/p/hardware-is-hard/</guid><description>Introduction to Hardware Hardware. What exactly is it? Why is it important. Why is it hard? Since the dawn of time there has been hardware engineers.
The Midwest is an area known for manufacturing excellence. Its unique geographic location, mild climate, and proximity make it desirable for the development of hardware products. My goal is to explore building hardware in Columbus and its surround areas. I hope you will join me on learning more on my journey to building hardware quicker.</description></item></channel></rss>