<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hardware development on MLL Electronics</title><link>https://mllelectronics.com/categories/hardware-development/</link><description>Recent content in Hardware development on MLL Electronics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mllelectronics.com/categories/hardware-development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Lean Hardware Methodologies</title><link>https://mllelectronics.com/p/lean-hardware-methodologies/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mllelectronics.com/p/lean-hardware-methodologies/</guid><description>The Lean Methodologies The concept of Lean is a guiding philosphy that focuses on creating value with fewer resources and less waste. This philosphy focuses on the elimination of non-value add activities and waste from business by focusing on the needs of the customer. The customer itself is intentionally ambigious at first but then requires introspection regarding the entire process flow.
Primary users of Lean Methodologies are Manufacuturing companies and Software Development companies.</description></item><item><title>Hardware is Hard</title><link>https://mllelectronics.com/p/hardware-is-hard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mllelectronics.com/p/hardware-is-hard/</guid><description>Introduction to Hardware Hardware. What exactly is it? Why is it important. Why is it hard? Since the dawn of time there has been hardware engineers.
The Midwest is an area known for manufacturing excellence. Its unique geographic location, mild climate, and proximity make it desirable for the development of hardware products. My goal is to explore building hardware in Columbus and its surround areas. I hope you will join me on learning more on my journey to building hardware quicker.</description></item></channel></rss>